our demands yes you must give us
наши требования да вы должны нам отдать
Belgorod Rostov and Krasnodar I'm
Белгород Ростов и Краснодар вас
listening to you we can't give you Belgorod
слушаю мы не можем Вам отдать Белгород
Rostov and Krasnodar Pan Andrey Okay
Ростов и Краснодар Пан Андрей О'кей То
So you don't want
есть вы не хотите
peace Pan Andrey hello
мира Пан Андрей здравствуйте
hello Hello something Do you want to
здравствуйте Здравствуйте что-то Хотите
ask I understand you are some kind of
спросить Я так понимаю вы какой-то
blogger Yes Russian
блогер Да российский
no yes something you damn I remember you've been
не да чтото вы блин я помню вы больше
sitting here for more than a year now half a year
года уже тут постоянно сидите полгода
Pan Andrey is no longer a pan They started
Пан Андрей не уже паном Меня начали
calling me the last meeting and in
называть последней встре же ина
general I already You probably missed it I
вообще я уже Вы наверное упустили я вам
told you I lay down a little after the accident for six months
говорил я после ДТП полгода немножко
but already with So what  nephews
прилёг но уже с Так что этом племянники
put this cloud
поставили эту тучку
Yas understood nothing And
Ясь ничего понял А
support
поддержите
the special operation I call it war No I don't
спецоперацию я называю это войной Нет не
support And you no I don't support And
поддерживаю А вы нет не поддерживаю А
who is the wine that Zamir And you For peace I
кто вино что Замир А вы За мир Я
Andrey you For peace I know they have such For
Андрей вы За мир я знаю им есть такое За
peace
мир
Just you Well you say no  I support
Просто вы Ну вы говорите не поддерживаю
the war, so for peace Yes, yes, I am for peace I am
войну значит За мир Да да я за мир я Я
for all the occupiers to be killed so that they do
за то чтобы всех оккупантов тили чтобы
not run away
не убежали
Well, what kind of peace is this, let's have peace,
Ну какой же это мир это давайте мир
look at the world -  this is the absence of occupiers
смотрите мир - это отсутствие оккупантов
on our land is true this will be
на нашей земле правда это будет
peace let's do it this way do you agree that when
мир давайте так Вы согласны что когда
all the Russian occupiers in Ukraine either
все русские оккупанты в Украине либо
will be or run away
будут либо убегут настанет
peace will come Andrey before we start talking
мир Андрей пока мы не начали разговор
let's do it this way you tried to talk to me twice
Давайте Так вы два раза пытались со мной
I tried and twice you
поговорить Я пытался и два ра вы матом
interrupted with obscenities  our conversation and left,
прерывали наш разговор и уходили дава
of course, we will not say goodbye together,
конечно дружно не попрощаемся разговор
without interrupting the conversation, you agree, it is
не прерывая Вы согласны
good that there are occupiers, well, you
Хорошо хорошо что там оккупанты ну вы
agree that when all the occupiers are at
согласны что когда все оккупанты будут у
or flee from Ukraine, peace will come,
или убегут из Украины настанет мир
true, after negotiations, we talked, they
правда после переговоров поговорили Они
left, it is better, true, they can flee
ушли так лучше правда могут и убежать и
without negotiations, the point is  the same for us
без переговоров суть же на Нам же
the main thing is peace
главное мир
the truth the main thing is that people don't die
правда Главное чтобы не гибли люди
now instill say the shooting
сейчас всели говорить стрельба
has stopped absolutely right
прекратилась абсолютно правильно
look if all the occupiers and run away they
смотрите если все оккупанты и убегут ди
will stop dying
перестанут гибнуть
the truth if your president and our
правда если ваш президент и наш
president give the command to cease
президент отдаст команду прекратить
fire super cool people will stop
огонь Супер Круто я люди перестанут
dying yes let's watch I am ours
гибнуть да давайте смотрите Я наш
president you are your president Let's
президент вы ваш президент Давайте
try to
попробуем
discuss some of our find a common
обсудить какие-то наши найти общий
denominator yes let's let's then
знаменатель да давайте давайте значит
look I as president Zelensky
смотрите Я как президент Зеленский
say then look our demands
говорю значит смотрите наши требования
yes you owe us  give Belgorod Rostov
да вы должны нам отдать Белгород Ростов
and Krasnodar I'm
и Краснодар вас
listening to you we can't give you Belgorod
слушаю мы не можем Вам отдать Белгород
Rostov and Krasnodar Pan Andrey Okay
Ростов и Краснодар Пан Андрей О'кей То
So you don't want
есть вы не хотите
peace We want peace like this And what are your
мира Мы хотим мира так А какие у вас
conditions we can offer you instead of
условия мы Вам можем предложить место
Belgorod Rostov and Krasnodar other
Белгорода Ростова и Краснодара другие
territories there Almost ready  cottage
территории там Почти готовы коттеджные
villages nature protected area
посёлки природа территория охраняемая
Magadan Kolyma a little bit of
район Магадан Колыма немножко
Vorkuta reparations at the same time
Воркуты репарации заодно
dig up there with I understood it seems to me that
накопать там с я понял мне кажется что
your negotiating position is very
ваша переговорная позиция очень
weak therefore Because those
слабенькая поэтому Потому что те
territories are of no interest to anyone here
территории никого не интересуют вот
Belgorod Krasnodar and Rostov are possible Well you
Белгород Краснодар и Ростов можно Ну вы
know while we were talking here they
знаете пока мы с вами общались тут мне
tell me  what let's give us
говорят что давайте ещ мы на
another Bryansk region you will give us Staro
ещё брянщину вы нам отдадите Старо
Bryansk region too We won't give it up we can add
брянщину тоже Не отдадим можем добавить
Vorkuta Pony there are the same cottage
Воркуту Поня там такие же коттеджные
villages with 100 people in that look It
посёлки по 100 человек в то смотрите Вы
turns out you Vladimir Putin are
получается получается вы Владимир Путин
not interested in negotiations you don't
не заинтересованы в переговорах вы не
want to look well it's very simple look
хотите смотри ну очень просто смотрите
you to us  give Rostov Krasnodar Belgorod
вы нам отдаёте Ростов Краснодар Белгород
and Bryansk and everything and  we stop fighting with you
и Брянск и всё и и мы прекращаем с вами
you are still with us just
воевать вы с нами всё ж просто
listen we convinced you there
послушайте мы вас всё-таки убеждали там
is a sea there Okhotsk look you for you
море есть Охотское смотрите Вы для вас
what is
Что
more important some territories Belgorod
важнее какие-то территории Белгород
Bryansk Kursk Rostov Krasnodar or people
Брянск Курск Ростов Краснодар или люди
so that people do not die you want
чтобы люди не гибли вы же хотите чтобы
people not to die  it's very simple, you give
люди не гибли так очень просто с отдаёте
us these territories and that's it, no one dies,
нам эти территории и всё Никто не гибнет
Mr. Andrey, in my opinion, why not Andrey but
Пан Андрей по-моему Зачем не Андрей а
Vladimir Vladimir, we communicate as two
Владимир Владимир Мы же как два
presidents, but soon they will
президента общаемся а Да скоро они
finish their terms, let's do it, let's do it in the image of
заканчивают сроки мы давайте мы в образе
presidents, let's do it, well, well, I still
президентов Давайте ну Ну я всё-таки
propose  I insist that you Magadan
предлагаю Настоятельно вам Магадан
Kolyma and Varkutka look well Let's do
Колыма и Варкута хорошо смотрите Давайте
it this way we take Rostov Yes
Так мы так забираем Ростов Да
Krasnodar Belgorod Bryansk Vorkuta Kolyma
Краснодар Белгород Брянск Воркуту колыму
and Magadan there we will make for you
и Магадан там мы для вас сделаем вот
these All in short who fought Yes we will
этих Все короче которые воевали Да мы их
pour them there We will take all these
туда полим Всё мы забираем в состав
regions into Ukraine Yes and
Украины эти области Да вот и
that's it  then war agree
прекращается тогда война согласны
agree So this is how we create troikas
согласен Значит так мы создаём тройки
they you drink who is 25 years old
они вам выпи кому 25 лет
Who you you look at you you we will
Кому вас вас смотрите вас вы мы сейчас
finish the conversation now Yes you will come out  here they'll
договорим Да вы выйдете вот тут за
grab you by the arms and take you
дверки так вас под ручки возьмут отвезут
to Gaga. There you'll be tried as a
в Гагу Да там вас будут судить как
war criminal. Well, basically, you
военного преступника Ну в принципе вы
already are. Who is Gaga, this
уже А кто такая Гага это
Lady. Why are you
Леди Почему вы
interrupting who Gaga is. Do you know who
перебивайте кто такая Гага Знаете вы кто
Gaga is? You know, right. So, look, let
така Гага знаете да Так вот смотрите
's stop there.  so our
останавливаемся на том значит наша
position we take from you Belgorod Kursk
позиция мы забираем у вас Белгород Курск
Bryansk Rostov Krasnodar so China and
Брянск Ростов Краснодар так Китаю и
Japan according to their there Let them
Японии по ихнему там Пусть они
divide Vladivostok and the Far
соглашению поделят Владивосток и Дальний
East by agreement Yes Buryatia is independent Tatarstan
Восток Да Бурятия независимая Татарстан
Independent in the Caucasus a couple of parades
Независимый на Кавказе пара парад
of sovereignties and the Caucasian
суверенитетов и Кавказская
Federal Republic Yes Udmurtia
Федеративная Республика Да Удмуртия
is free Bashkartastan is free uh
свободна башкартастан свободный ээ
Tatarstan is free St. Petersburg  separates into a
Татарстан свободный Питер отделяется в
region called Free Ingria with the capital in
регион свободная ингрия со столицей в
St. Petersburg yes they will rename it
санкт-петербурге да переименуют е правда
to some normal name Yes
в нормальное какое-то название Да
Ingerman Nadya Yes Vo uh the
ингерман Надя Да Во ээ остатки
Muscovites
московщина
know the rest Let them do whatever they want Yes uh
знает Пусть что там хотят делают Да ээ
we will give it to the British under the British
отдаём под Британское под британский
protectorate Let them decide there what to
протекторат Пусть они там решат что там
do with him dakho And you personally Vladimir
с ним делать дахо А вы лично Владимир
Vladimirovich go Gaga everything The conversation
Владимирович идёте Гагу всё Разговор
is over first Let Gaga come to
окончен во-первых Пусть Гага приедет ко
me note what are you note Everything we have agreed
мне ноте что вы ноте Всё мы договорили
goodbye stand afraid stand afraid
свидания стоять боятся стоять боятся
Gaga No it is not finished will
Гага Нет уж не окончено
do we will  insist on your
сделаете мы будем настаивать на своём
offer Magadan kalyma 25
предложении Магадан калыма 25
Magadan you will not Gaga there will be
Магадана вам не будет Гага будет там
better
лучше
conditions in Magadan there will be all sorts of small
условия в Магадан будут всякие мелкие
fry such as rifles and so on And
сошки такие как стрелковые и так далее А
for you a separate camera in Gaga so that it is
для вас отдель камера в гаге чтоб
publicly for the whole world Yes Gaga it sounds
публично на весь мир Да Гага это звучит
beautiful as bre sits and Magadan  kalyma
красиво как бре сидит а Магадан калыма
this somehow sounds more or less clear
это как-то звучит уже более-менее мисто
and understandable now look you and I
и понятно тепер смотрите вы мы с Вами
agreed that I wouldn't leave like that and we said
договорились чтоб я так не уходил а мы
goodbye normally Yes that's what you
попрощались нормально Да так вот вы
said
говорили
Masha I wasn't hit by a car Well you had an accident
Маши меня не сбила машина Ну ДТП у вас
and after that what were you there  -Something bad with you
да после этого вы там что-то плохо у вас
No, everything is good with me with your
Да нет у меня всё хорошо вашими
prayers pa Andrey not I pray to you
молитвами па Андрей не я молюсь у вас
like to my uncle  Slava was And
как у дяди Славы было А
what about D Slava
что Д Слава
already you
уже вы
are anticipating he is not yet he is just in the
предвкушаю он ещ не он как раз в
process of excruciatingly you are not of
процессе мучительно вы не от
the world at all not a Christian at all I will
мира вообще не христианин вообще я
say more here even Christians
больше скажу у нас даже христиане
are happy watching videos every evening
радуются смотрят видео каждый вечер
watching videos how in short there some
смотрят видео как короче там какому-то
Russian soldier got his head torn off  front and
русскому солдату оторвало на фронте и
enjoy I think why Christians don't
наслаждаются Я думаю почему христиане не
say Glory to Jesus Christ But they say
говорят Слава Иисусу Христу А говорят
Glory to
Слава
Ukraine I will say so eh Christ said
Украине скажу так э Христос как говорил
yes
да
whoever comes to Ukraine
кто в Украину
with weapons will
придёт с оружием тому
be torn off with a kid from a drone and therefore what kind of
оторвёт с кидом с дрона и поэтому какой
sermon is this Christ said from Matthew
проповеди это Христос говорил от Матвея
1732 Yes and the one who  took
1732 Да и уда тот который взял
the silver coins you your 30 silver coins
серебряники вы свои 30 Серебренников
Where next I will tell you this look
Куда дальше я вам вот что скажу смотрите
about the silver coins look you a sign from
насчёт Серебренников смотрите вам знак
above there was an accident but you did not understand you should have
свыше был ДТП но вы не поняли Вы должны
listened that they are sending you a signal you are a
были внемлить Что вам посылают сигнал Вы
Christian I am not Who are you I am a
христианин Я нет А кто вы Я мусульманин
Muslim a Muslim you are not a Muslim
мусульманин это вы не мусульманин не
Call the
Позовите
Muslims Pan Andrey don't scare me with death
мусульман Пан Андрей вы смертью меня не
when a Man
пугайте когда Человек
is born it is already written when he is  will die
рождается уже написано когда он умрёт
my Absolutely right Yes it is written
мо Абсолютно верно Да у него написано
where he will die but there Yes the director makes
где умрёт но там Да режиссёр вносит
adjustments he looks at something this
коррективы он смотрит что-то этот
very let's somehow change the script
очень давайте мы как-то изменим сценарий
and for example his son sits there says
а сидит там например его его сын говорит
dad dad let's in short now there is such a topic in
батя бать давай короче сейчас такая тема
short so that here  we saw yesterday in
есть короче чтобы вот э видели вчера в
Donetsk
Донецке
uh news a Russian war correspondent was hit by a
ээ новость российского военкор сбила
car at a crosswalk we're like ta-
машина на переходе мы такие
da-da-da we read the second news you know it
тада дадада читаем вторую новость выв
turns out the driver was uh the head of
оказывается за рулём был э начальник
some commandant's office there in Donetsk like
какой-то комендатуры там Донецкой типа
Bingo In short one department hit the second one
Бинго Короче одно отдело сбило второго
one in the morgue the other one is generally Bingo
типа один в морге другой вообще Бинго
so that's what you  are you happy about the
так вот чему вы радуетесь
tragedy it's not a tragedy if you killed
трагеди это не трагедия если бы Вы убили
our soldier you would have gone out on the battlefield I would have
солдата нашего вышли бы на поле боя я бы
said yes the man won Yes you
сказал да человек победил Да вы
are happy when
радуетесь когда гибнут
people die Radu look if your soldier Yes he
люди Раду смотри если ваш солдат Да в
died in an accident what difference does it make to him did
ДТП его не стало какая разница ему
you put it to this Rukh on the contrary [ __ ]
вы приложили к этому Рух наоборот сри у
us as they say will perish our armed Like
нас как говорят сгинуть наши вооружен Як
dew in the sun Yes they themselves because
роса на солнце Да они сами потому что
the Lord Yes he sees he thinks Not me not
Господь Да видит он думает Не я не
just me  I'll put Strelkov in
просто я Стрелкова посажу в
jail so that Putin will put him in jail Yes, I'm
тюрьму чтобы Путин его посадил Да я
Prigozhin Imagine Jesus Christ sitting there to
пригожина Прикинь там сидит исус фом
his dad and saying Well, come on,
бате своей и говорит Да ну блин Давай
well, it's nice that Gro during
короче ну пригоже что гро во время
the rebellion, dad says not Sonny There's a
мятежа батя говорит не Сынуля Есть тема
more interesting topic What does he say and he says
поинтереснее Какая говорит а он говорит
Look, now we'll let him go  him to
Смотри сейчас мы его типа отпустим его в
Africa and then in short
Африку а потом короче
badaboom and there can't be such a scenario
бадабум а не может быть такого сценария
Bat says I've seen scenarios like this
Бат говорит я ещё не такие сценарии
and in short
видал и короче
Oops really blew up in the plane and
Опа реально в самолёт взорвался а
Strelkov thinks Wow
стрелков такой думает Нифига себе Вот
this is what Novorossians built so whoever is
это Новорос построили так вот тот кто
up there has a very specific
там наверху у него очень специфическое
sense of humor  and I'll tell you I think
чувство юмора и я вам скажу Мне кажется
that I'm a seer I think that
что вот я провидец Мне кажется что у
he also has a rather interesting
него тоже заготовлен довольно интересный
scenario prepared for you and for your family so in
сценарий для вас и для вашей семьи так в
this plot there may be Prim And you there
этом сюжете может быть Прим А вы там
Ask me, I'm not the one writing the plots
Спросите не я же сюжеты пишу
You really really do you understand there are
Вы реально реально вы понимаете есть
different Varias  I'm Gloom Yes I'm Gloom I
разны Вари я Глум Да я Глум я
God I probably
Боже поди
thought that I would watch some
думал что я буду смотреть видео какие-то
kind of cruel videos And get pleasure from it
такие жестокие Да и получать от этого
I get I really if
наслаждение Я получаю я реально вот если
in the evening I didn't watch some video
я вечером не посмотрел какой-то видосик
you know with the torn off occupier I think
знаете с оторванной оккупанта Я думаю
damn somehow not right I
блин как-то не так
go there is a buzz and you understand you warmth
захожу есть кайф и ты понимаешь ва тепло
runs from the tip of your fingers on the
пробегает от кончика ваших пальцев на
Notik up you feel like
Нотик вверх вы чуете как вос
at the same time both Buddhists and  Christian and
одновременно и буддисты и християнин и
Kren at this time I merge in me all
крени в это время я во мне сливаются все
religions so Kundalini
религии так поднимается Кундалини
rises chakras open Everything in short at once so I
открываются чакры Всё короче сразу так я
understood you I say I am in this Yes I
понял вы Я говорю я в этом Да я
enjoy Yes when the occupiers and in
наслаждаюсь Да когда оккупанты причём в
huge quantities Yes there is a serial
огромных количествах Да есть серийный
maniac I see there are in short videos yes
маняк я смотрю есть короче видосы да
when  they cover said if a girl
когда накрывают сказали если девочку
was hit by a girl I am also happy about the girl
сбили девочку Я тоже радуюсь про девочку
I did not say about the girl I did not say
Я не говорил про девочку Я не говорил
no Look at the recording don't say what
нет Посмотрите запись не говори се что
you meant about your family I
вы имели в виду насчёт вашей семьи Я
say that God sees everything Yes and the curse
говорю что Бог всё видит Да и проклятие
Up to the seventh generation can be Curse
До седьмого колена может быть Проклятие
yes that  look at you, the accident was not
да то есть на вас смотрите ДТП было не
just like that, well, there are no coincidences,
просто так ну не бывает же случайностей
so this happened  Accident Well
так как вот получилось это ДТП Ну
tell me with these new rules for driving through a
скажите с этими новыми правилами проезда
roundabout I didn't realize
кругового движения что-то я не сообразил
something didn't communicate always drove through But here they didn't
чтото не сооб всегда проезжали А тут не
realize I drove through according to the old rules
сообразили проезжал по старым правилам
automatically Yeah, well what
на автомате Да а а что же что ж такое
happened that you had to somehow
случилось что вам пришлось как-то
go through a little bit after that  there
проходить немножко после этого там
rehabilitation or whatever you went
реабилитацию или что что вы проходили На
through God's will be done The Almighty was so
всё воля божья нала Всевышний так
pleased that's right that's right the Almighty
радился вот да то есть Всевышний Да
Yeah there the son says dad let's have him m
ээ там сынок говорит бать давай его м
dad says no no look Let's
уже батя говорит нет нет смотри Давай мы
give him a tremor like that yeah let's have
сделаем ему тремор такой да давай сейчас
him on this circular ring now  I'll have
его на этом круговом кольце сейчас
a little bang yes he yes what he didn't
немножко бахну да он да что он не
figure out then he'll
разобрался потом он
sit for six months Yes but we want I want
полгода посидит Да но мы хотим Я хочу
son says dad Let's finish this
сынок говорит бать Давай завершим это
in short let's go his dad says No I want
короче давай его батя говорит Нет я хочу
him to die did you see how Uncle Slava
чтобы он почил ты видел как Дядя Слава
son says Uncle Slava says
сынок такой говорит Дядя Слава говорит
look he comes in  Jesus there in
на посмотри заходит Иисус туда в
Roulette This is Uncle Slava not necessary for
Рулетку Вот это Дядя Слава не надо для
him  some kind of Kara to come up with and
него какую-то Кару придумать и
they came up with sgo sre now like a vegetable
придумали сго сре сейчас как овощ такой
barely moves eats drinks with difficulty this is
на еле двигается ест пьёт с трудом это
also not without reason all this nasty stuff
же тоже неспроста вот эти все гадости
that you Uncle Slava said to
которые ты Дядя Слава говорил чтобы
support the UVO of people in Ukraine it Everything
поддерживал УВО людей в Украине оно Всё
returned as an old woman because Slava is the
вернулось старицей потому что Слава
director who writes there  script and I
режиссёра которые там пишут сценарий и я
see in your eyes that some script is waiting for you too, it has
вижу по вашим глазам что вас тоже ждёт
already been written and they are
какой-то сценарий тоже написан уже и они
rewriting it, improving it, adding
переписывают усовершенствуем добавляют
colors, adding new characters, do you
красок добавляют новых персонажей вы
think that next time you can
думаете что вы в следующий раз можете
go on a circular ring road Not by yourself But with your
ехать на круговом кольце Не сами А с
granddaughter and
внучкой с
son and there they can  punish they will say look
сыном и там могут покарать скажут смотри
he will be bored in hell he needs to
ему в аду будет скучно самому нужно
take everyone himself And the son says No why do
забрать всех А сынок говорит Не зачем
they have anything to do with it And the dad says no look son
причём они А батя говорит нет смотри сын
you have collected all the sins for them atoned for it Yes
ты за них собрал все грехи искупил Да
this Let him also isp so that's
этот Пусть тоже испт так
when it is with at the moment when
вот когда это с в момен ког
this truck in front of his windshield
эту фуру перед своим лобовым
glass you will remember my
стеклом вы вспомните мои
words of tragedy more as Stanislavsky
слова трагизма больше как Станиславский
said I do not
говорил не
believe said goodbye calmly without ma write on
верю попрощались спокойно без ма пись на
my Telegram right now axis VN
мий Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
apok this is very and very important YouTube is busy
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
with us through scarg Orcs in shadows ban and very
нас через скарг Орки в теней бан и дуже
many videos I dont show people at times I dont
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams Thats why in order for
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
me Mali operational connections
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
are written right now and while there in telegram
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
OKRIM video also interesting and useful
окрим видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we will oblige you with
информация и мы повинни з вами тримати
constant operational connection
постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine subscribe
YouTube Слава Украине подпишись